Guide to the Athletics Department Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Programs
  - Football
    - Baylor, October 3, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - TCU, October 31, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Texas, November 7, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Arizona State, September 18, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Baylor, October 2, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Lamar, September 25, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Texas A&M, October 9, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - TCU, October 30, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - (26th Annual Red & White Spring Game), April 23, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Baylor, October 1, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Texas Tech, November 19, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Miami-Ohio, September 15, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Louisville, September 29, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - TCU, November 3, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Rice, December 1, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Boston College (Cotton Bowl), January 1, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Washington, September 21, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - SMU, October 19, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Texas, November 9, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Arkansas, October 25, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - TCU, November 1, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Rice, November 29, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Oklahoma State, September 12, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Sam Houston State, September 26, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Baylor, October 3, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Texas, November 7, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Temple, (Homecoming), November 14, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Texas Tech, November 21, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Texas A&M, October 8, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Tulsa, October 15, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - TCU, October 29, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Texas "Dad's Day", November 5, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Wyoming, November 12, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Rice, November 26, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - UNLV, September 2, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Arizona State, September 23, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Baylor, October 7, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - SMU, October 21, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Texas, November 11, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Texas Tech, November 25, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Rice, December 2, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Arizona ("Coca-Cola" Bowl), (Tokyo), 1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Nevada-Las Vegas, September 8, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Rice, September 29, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Texas A&M, October 13, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - TCU, (Homecoming), November 3, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Eastern Washington, November 17, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Louisiana Tech, August 31, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Illinois, September 21, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Baylor, October 5, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Texas, November 9, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Michigan, September 26, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Southwestern Louisiana, October 3, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - USC, September 4, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Baylor, October 2, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - SMU, (Homecoming), October 16, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Texas, November 4, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Cincinnati, November 13, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Mississippi, October 22, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Kansas (Fort Worth Bowl), December 23, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Southern Mississippi, December 1, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - TCU (Texas Bowl), December 28, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Texas State, September 4, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - UTEP, September 10, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Tulane, September 25, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Mississippi State, October 9, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - UCF, November 5, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Tulsa, November 13, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Southern Mississippi (Conference USA Championship), 2011 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Penn State (TicketCity Bowl), January 2, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Vanderbilt (BBVA Compass Bowl), January 4, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Championship Publications
  - Football
    - Veer-T Offense, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Mad Dog Defense, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Spring Football, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Spring Football Prospectus, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Basketball (Men's)
    - NCAA Tournament, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 51st Annual National Invitation Tournament, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Division I Men’s Basketball Championship First & Second Rounds, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Southwest Conference Men’s Basketball, 1994-95 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Southwest Conference Men’s Basketball, 1995-96 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Basketball (Women's)
    - Southwest Conference Women’s, 1995-96 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - (1st Women’s Southwest Conference), Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - (Invitational), February 7-9, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Arkansas, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - (2nd Southwest Conference), March 8-10, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Track & Field
    - Texas Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women Track and Field Championships, May 1-2, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 62nd Annual Men’s/ Women’s NCAA Track and Field Championships, May 30-June 4, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - (1st Championship), June 7-8, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - (District Championship), June 5, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - (District Championship), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - (Houston Jaycee Invitational Track Meet), December 16, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - (“Meet the Champions”), May, 31, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - (Houston Jaycee Invitational Track Meet), November 29, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - (Men SWC Champs), 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - (Southwest Conference Championship), May 14-15, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - (62nd Annual Men’s, 2nd Annual Women’s NCAA Champ.), May 30-June 4, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Clay Target
    - 24th Annual Intercollegiate Clay Target Championships, April 22-26, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Golf
    - National Golf Champions, 1956-1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - (57th Annual National Collegiate Championship), June 20-26, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - (7th Annual All-American Intercollegiate Invitational), March 29-April 1, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - (15th Annual All-American Intercollegiate Championship), April 16-19, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - (16th Annual All-American Intercollegiate Championship), April 14-18, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Swimming
    - Swimming and diving Championships, February 26-28, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - (57th Annual NCAA Championship, Harvard Univ.), March 27-29, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Cross-Country
    - (Southwest Conference Championship), October 31, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Volleyball
    - (13th Annual Invitational), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - (14th Annual UH Invitational), 1980 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Mexico Sports Univ. Institute, November 14, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - (15th Annual UH Invitational), 1981 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - (NCAA Division I S. Regional Championship), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- UH Athletic Publications
  - Basketball (Men's)
    - Cougars Inside Houston Sports, January 1981 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Cougars Inside Houston Sports, January 1983 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Cougars Inside Sports, March/April, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Yearbook, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Yearbook, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Texas Southern, Scorecard, December 15, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Illinois-Chicago, Scorecard, December 12, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Baylor, Scorecard, January 19, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - The Elvin Hayes Jersey Retirement Ceremony, December 20, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Basketball (Women's)
    - Yearbook, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Yearbook, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Football
    - The Cougar Growl, undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - The Cougar Growl, October-November, undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Texas Football Magazine, November 25, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Southwest Conference Football Magazine - Houston vs. RIce, September 15, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Southwest Conference Football Magazine - Houston vs. Carolina, September 21, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Southwest Conference Football Magazine - Houston vs. Wyoming, November 24, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Southwest Conference Football Magazine - Houston vs. Tulsa, December 1, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - The EXtra Alumni Magazine, Winter 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Cougars Inside Houston Sports, February 1980 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Cougars Inside Houston Sports, November 1980 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Cougars Inside Houston Sports, December 1980 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Cougars Inside Houston Sports, December 1981 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Cougars Inside Houston Sports, October 1982 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Team Photo Night, November 1, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Cougars Inside Sports, June 1989 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Cougar Update, Summer 1996 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Miscellaneous Athletic Publications and Clippings
  - Big Time Baseball, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Texas Football News Magazine, November 11, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Game Plan College Football, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - The EXtra Alumni Magazine, December 1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Texas Sports Football Preview, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Astro Sports, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Texas Football (Summer Issue), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - The University of Tulsa Football Magazine, September 7, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "PRIDE” UH System Magazine, Winter 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - GTE Academic All American Football Team, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 81st Drake Relays, April 27-28, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Sportsman & Sportswoman of the Year, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Sports Illustrated, December 22, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Sports Illustrated, April 18, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Sports Illustrated, January 14, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Sports Illustrated, May 8, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Sports Illustrated, April 23, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Sports Illustrated, November 12, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Sports Illustrated, March, 7, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Sports Illustrated, June 25, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Sports Illustrated, May 26, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Sports Illustrated, April 20, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Sports Illustrated, August 17, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Sports Illustrated, August 26, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Sports Illustrated, December 28, 1992-January 4, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Scrapbook (Ovs item 1)
  - Poster (Bayou Bucket), Team Picture (undated), Misc. (Ovs folder 1)
  - Andre Ware (Ovs folder 2)
  - Baseball (Ovs folder 3)
  - Basketball (Ovs folder 4)
  - Football (Ovs folder 5)
  - Golf (Ovs folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous (Ovs folder 7)
  - Tennis (Ovs folder 8)
  - Track (Ovs folder 9)
  - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings for Track and Field, 1966-1967 (Ovs box 1, Item 1)